<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Anthony Cho]]></title><description><![CDATA[CS '20 @ Rice. Incoming SWE @ Grand Rounds.]]></description><link>http://anthonycho.net</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 06:43:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Preparing for the Road Ahead]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is probably my last winter break as a student. Next semester, I'll (knock on wood) graduate Rice with a BS in Computer Science. It's crazy to think about.]]></description><link>http://anthonycho.net/posts/12/24/personal</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://anthonycho.net/posts/12/24/personal</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 10:24:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This is probably my last winter break as a student. Next semester, I’ll be (knock on wood) graduating Rice with a BS in Computer Science. It’s crazy to think about. This morning as I was walking my dog and enjoying the crisp morning air of Oregon, I couldn’t help but feel a tinge of sadness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49267796113_97197e6c6b_o.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;a picture of my dog teddy&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before I came home for the break, I grabbed coffee with one of my closest friends who had just graduated and we reminsced about our past 4 years at Rice together. I asked him how he felt about leaving Rice and he said something that really stuck out to me. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We spend so much time thinking about the past and grinding for the future that we squeeze out the present”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I think he captured what had really been lodged in my heart for some time now. This uneasy feeling of misplaced nothingness, doing so much yet feeling so little. I remembered then, another memorable quote from the final blog post of a retiring software engineer and founder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My time for doing has come to an end. My time for being has begun”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t know if this is selfish or naive of me, but I would very much like those two times to coincide in my life, for all of my life. I don’t want to squeeze out the present anymore, but to enjoy and savor it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s the reason behind V3, the third overhaul of my personal website. This will hopefully be a centralized place for me, for the things that I care about and the thoughts in my head.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>