<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Anthony Cho]]></title><description><![CDATA[SWE @ Grand Rounds. CS '20 @ Rice. Writing about my life and things that matter to me.]]></description><link>http://anthonycho.net</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 06:44:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[A Merry Christmas]]></title><description><![CDATA[Since my birthday (Dec 13) and christmas are so close to one another, I've recently been getting so much love from family, friends, and my so. And last week, as I was in the ER I distinctly remember my dad and sister waiting patiently next to my bed all night long.]]></description><link>http://anthonycho.net/posts/personal/a-merry-christmas</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://anthonycho.net/posts/personal/a-merry-christmas</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 09:54:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Since my birthday (Dec 13) and christmas are so close to one another, I’ve recently been getting so much love from family, friends, and my so. And last week, as I was in the ER I distinctly remember my dad and sister waiting patiently next to my bed all night long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I haven’t felt this thankful for the people around me in so long. Today, I enjoyed some beautiful family time leisurely enjoying a rare moment when all of us are together. We started the morning off at one of my favorite brunch places in Portland and honestly the US: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.yelp.com/biz/screen-door-portland&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopener noreferrer&quot;&gt;Screen Door&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49272734356_5244b56ea2_c.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;screen door&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My future brother-in-law Sean Lee gifted me a Fuji XF35mmF2 R WR last night so this Christmas Eve I got the chance to play around with it and it was truly a thing of beauty. Really enjoying this lens for portraits. In general, although I’m a complete novice, I think I’ve already fallen in love with the natural color of my Fuji X-T30.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After brunch, we lazed around, drank coffee, ate dinner, and watched Klaus. Klaus was honestly one of the most beautiful things I’ve ever watched. Also, my sister roasted these delicious chestnuts and I made a nice V60 pour over with a Stumptown blend. It was nice. It felt right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49272735776_da7a9e39e5_c.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;my family&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>