<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Anthony Cho]]></title><description><![CDATA[CS '20 @ Rice. Incoming SWE @ Grand Rounds.]]></description><link>http://anthonycho.net</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 09:46:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[A Barrier to Entry]]></title><description><![CDATA[When I came into Rice as a freshman, coding was a completely foreign concept to me. It was challenging in the most infuriating and trivial ways.]]></description><link>http://anthonycho.net/posts/coding/a-barrier-to-entry</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://anthonycho.net/posts/coding/a-barrier-to-entry</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 08:53:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;When I came into Rice as a freshman, coding was a completely foreign concept to me. It was challenging in the most infuriating and trivial ways. Now, with just a little bit more experience under my belt I laugh at those frustrations along with millions of other developers. The classic misplaced semicolon breaking your entire program or a misjudgement in variable assignment leading to some discrete mutation bug. It’s now become a part of development (oof) and almost a rite of passage to becoming a developer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But for new developers, it’s so much more. When you don’t know what you don’t know, these tiny challenges can become a huge barrier to entry. And for those who are not privileged or lucky enough to meet the right mentorship or resources, it can be the end of something that could have been incredible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span
      class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-wrapper&quot;
      style=&quot;position: relative; display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;  max-width: 799px;&quot;
    &gt;
      &lt;a
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-link&quot;
    href=&quot;/static/313bd078e9e5a829e5da6458731b00ff/eecba/coding_meme.jpg&quot;
    style=&quot;display: block&quot;
    target=&quot;_blank&quot;
    rel=&quot;noopener&quot;
  &gt;
    &lt;span
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-background-image&quot;
    style=&quot;padding-bottom: 77.7221526908636%; position: relative; bottom: 0; left: 0; background-image: url(&apos;data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wBDABALDA4MChAODQ4SERATGCgaGBYWGDEjJR0oOjM9PDkzODdASFxOQERXRTc4UG1RV19iZ2hnPk1xeXBkeFxlZ2P/2wBDARESEhgVGC8aGi9jQjhCY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2P/wgARCAAQABQDASIAAhEBAxEB/8QAFwABAQEBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAQDBf/EABUBAQEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAIB/9oADAMBAAIQAxAAAAGfCGknpir/xAAbEAACAwADAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABAwACBBEiMv/aAAgBAQABBQLrLETPrqpfBg8Z9K6L/8QAFhEBAQEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAhAR/9oACAEDAQE/ASMn/8QAFBEBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEP/aAAgBAgEBPwE//8QAGhAAAgIDAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAECEBESMf/aAAgBAQAGPwI6atO8SP/EABsQAAMAAwEBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABESExYUFR/9oACAEBAAE/IdfTMS6hSi7cHBjSbm6Kudvw/9oADAMBAAIAAwAAABAo7//EABURAQEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABEQ/9oACAEDAQE/EGrP/8QAFREBAQAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAARD/2gAIAQIBAT8QZ//EABwQAAICAgMAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAERACExQXGB0f/aAAgBAQABPxBqGWyj7Bc/sqpfGrIrjB0QYSqY7gPMGrXNPXLn/9k=&apos;); background-size: cover; display: block;&quot;
  &gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;picture&gt;
        &lt;source
          srcset=&quot;/static/313bd078e9e5a829e5da6458731b00ff/8ac56/coding_meme.webp 240w,
/static/313bd078e9e5a829e5da6458731b00ff/d3be9/coding_meme.webp 480w,
/static/313bd078e9e5a829e5da6458731b00ff/a2266/coding_meme.webp 799w&quot;
          sizes=&quot;(max-width: 799px) 100vw, 799px&quot;
          type=&quot;image/webp&quot;
        /&gt;
        &lt;source
          srcset=&quot;/static/313bd078e9e5a829e5da6458731b00ff/5a194/coding_meme.jpg 240w,
/static/313bd078e9e5a829e5da6458731b00ff/8a430/coding_meme.jpg 480w,
/static/313bd078e9e5a829e5da6458731b00ff/eecba/coding_meme.jpg 799w&quot;
          sizes=&quot;(max-width: 799px) 100vw, 799px&quot;
          type=&quot;image/jpeg&quot;
        /&gt;
        &lt;img
          class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-image&quot;
          src=&quot;/static/313bd078e9e5a829e5da6458731b00ff/eecba/coding_meme.jpg&quot;
          alt=&quot;coding meme&quot;
          title=&quot;coding meme&quot;
          loading=&quot;lazy&quot;
          style=&quot;width:100%;height:100%;margin:0;vertical-align:middle;position:absolute;top:0;left:0;&quot;
        /&gt;
      &lt;/picture&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I remember my first hackathon, HackRice 6. I was incredibly lucky to be on a team of incredibly gifted and experienced developers who walked me gently through the process. They patiently answered my “stupid questions” and even tolerated it when I told the judges that we would have had a backend if we had just a few more minutes to add “sql” and “php”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following hackathons went similarly, with my ability to contribute growing rapidly. Finally, I remember feeling like I had “broken the barrier” to actually making cool stuff on my own when I went to PennApps XVI alone. There, an engineer and some random new friends from the University of Maryland (shout out to Tim Chen) spent hours in the middle of the night guiding me through the most difficult aspects of building my first “fullstack” webapp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I was so happy.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was so happy in fact that I decided I wanted to host a workshop for my fellow students back at Rice to build their first website within an hour. That year I was a freshman representative for Rice’s CS Club and one of the things the officer board was struggling most with was engagement. You have to understand, Rice is a tiny school of around 4,000 total undergrads. When I was a freshman, the previous graduating class of CS majors was something like 15-20 students.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That first workshop drew in nearly a 100 students. As I “taught” this &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/handsomericestudent/handsomericestudent.github.io&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopener noreferrer&quot;&gt;very simple workshop for making a github pages website&lt;/a&gt;, the other officers who were exceedingly talented and extraordinarily skilled in development were going around helping students in the same gentle, non-judgemental manner I had been helped by so many others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I realized, wow this is the beautiful and enduring face of the development community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now granted, it’s not always like that. I think my stackoverflow account was almost banned and somewhat accosted for asking stupid questions when I first made it. But even that aspect of the stackoverflow community has been addressed over the years, perhaps not fully but I’ve definitely noticed the change. And there are definitely many toxic aspects of the tech world that anybody who has even slightly experienced it can tell you about in great detail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In any case, the warmer side of the development community is remarkable and growing. There are countless more stories I could tell of the generosity of my peers and mentors, who have helped me so much. And when I ask them how I could ever repay them, they always tell me the same thing. Pay it forward.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A Whole New World]]></title><description><![CDATA[I've been spending a lot of time watching youtube videos about photography and it's been actually very eye opening. What I love about picking up new hobbies is that often times I'll stumble into a whole new world and community of people united by some like minded passion, always a medium for human expression.]]></description><link>http://anthonycho.net/posts/photography/a-whole-new-world</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://anthonycho.net/posts/photography/a-whole-new-world</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 11:00:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been spending a lot of time watching youtube videos about photography and it’s been actually very eye opening. What I love about picking up new hobbies is that often times I’ll stumble into a whole new world and community of people united by some like minded passion, always a medium for human expression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week, I’ve been focusing on learning how to edit photos. I subscribed to lightroom and started working on a few of the pictures I’d taken these past few weeks. I’m honestly amazed at how much of a difference it makes, even tiny adjustments. Here’s an example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;Pre Edit&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;Post Edit&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49327004632_1b0742a203_c.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;pre-edit sister and mom&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49327012877_0ff744e405_c.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;post-edit sister and mom&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, whether that difference is positive or not I am not sure. I imagine that there is bad and good in editing, but that the direction you take the editing is really what makes it your own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But dang, time flies by when you’re editing especially for someone like me who has no idea what he’s doing. I’ll spend an hour editing a photo and be proud, but then when I take another look I realize it’s horrible. Nevertheless, I get enjoyment out of an iterative process of learning like this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the first pictures I tried is of my Yuzu Shio from Afuri, a well known japanese ramen chain that established its first ramen shop outside of japan in Portland, OR. I first tried this ramen in Tokyo and I was so happy to hear they opened in Portland. The broth of this signature ramen is very bright and bursting with flavor. I wanted to see if I could convey all this with a tiny bit of editing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;Pre Edit&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;Post Edit&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49326910301_0b647c2de7_c.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;pre-edit of afuri ramen&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49326333588_0674ba4c74_c.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;post-edit of afuri ramen&quot;&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I used to dislike the idea of post editing and photoshop, long before I even started thinking about photography. I imagine that many people probably have had this same feeling, that technology is so powerful that it sometimes in some ways enroaches upon truth and authenticity, enroaches upon the beauty of seeing something for what it is, knowing that its representation is pure, unbiased. But I think there is more to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A map should be accurate and correct. A photograph, however, can be more than just an image. A photograph can be a story. And a story is not simply generated, it is written.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A Merry Christmas]]></title><description><![CDATA[Since my birthday (Dec 13) and christmas are so close to one another, I've recently been getting so much love from family, friends, and my so. And last week, as I was in the ER I distinctly remember my dad and sister waiting patiently next to my bed all night long.]]></description><link>http://anthonycho.net/posts/personal/a-merry-christmas</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://anthonycho.net/posts/personal/a-merry-christmas</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 09:54:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Since my birthday (Dec 13) and christmas are so close to one another, I’ve recently been getting so much love from family, friends, and my so. And last week, as I was in the ER I distinctly remember my dad and sister waiting patiently next to my bed all night long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I haven’t felt this thankful for the people around me in so long. Today, I enjoyed some beautiful family time leisurely enjoying a rare moment when all of us are together. We started the morning off at one of my favorite brunch places in Portland and honestly the US: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.yelp.com/biz/screen-door-portland&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopener noreferrer&quot;&gt;Screen Door&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49272734356_5244b56ea2_c.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;screen door&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My future brother-in-law Sean Lee gifted me a Fuji XF35mmF2 R WR last night so this Christmas Eve I got the chance to play around with it and it was truly a thing of beauty. Really enjoying this lens for portraits. In general, although I’m a complete novice, I think I’ve already fallen in love with the natural color of my Fuji X-T30.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After brunch, we lazed around, drank coffee, ate dinner, and watched Klaus. Klaus was honestly one of the most beautiful things I’ve ever watched. Also, my sister roasted these delicious chestnuts and I made a nice V60 pour over with a Stumptown blend. It was nice. It felt right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49272735776_da7a9e39e5_c.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;my family&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Preparing for the Road Ahead]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is probably my last winter break as a student. Next semester, I'll (knock on wood) graduate Rice with a BS in Computer Science. It's crazy to think about.]]></description><link>http://anthonycho.net/posts/personal/preparing-for-the-road-ahead</link><guid isPermaLink="false">http://anthonycho.net/posts/personal/preparing-for-the-road-ahead</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 10:24:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This is probably my last winter break as a student. Next semester, I’ll be (knock on wood) graduating Rice with a BS in Computer Science. It’s crazy to think about. This morning as I was walking my dog and enjoying the crisp morning air of Oregon, I couldn’t help but feel a tinge of sadness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/49267796113_0b8db3b98f_c.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;a picture of my dog teddy&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before I came home for the break, I grabbed coffee with one of my closest friends who had just graduated and we reminsced about our past 4 years at Rice together. I asked him how he felt about leaving Rice and he said something that really stuck out to me. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We spend so much time thinking about the past and grinding for the future that we squeeze out the present”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I think he captured what had really been lodged in my heart for some time now. This uneasy feeling of misplaced nothingness, doing so much yet feeling so little. I remembered then, another memorable quote from the final blog post of a retiring software engineer and founder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My time for doing has come to an end. My time for being has begun”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t know if this is selfish or naive of me, but I would very much like those two times to coincide in my life, for all of my life. I don’t want to squeeze out the present anymore, but to enjoy and savor it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s the reason behind V3, the third overhaul of my personal website. This will hopefully be a centralized place for me, for the things that I care about and the thoughts in my head.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>